<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Volleyverse</string>
    <string name="volleyverse_host">volleyverse.com</string>
    <string name="rest_url">https://volleyverse.com/wp-json/wp/v2/posts/?_embed</string>
    <string name="about_us_url">https://volleyverse.com/about-us/</string>
    <string name="partnerships_url">https://volleyverse.com/partnerships/</string>
    <string name="jobs_url">https://volleyverse.com/jobs/</string>
    <string name="privacy_and_cookie_policy_url">https://volleyverse.com/privacy-cookie-policy/</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_url">https://volleyverse.com/terms-of-use/</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_feedback">Feedback</string>

    <string name="about_us_body">
        The seed for Volleyverse was planted as a result of a chance happening with an
        international women’s volleyball tournament in Basel, Switzerland back in the mid 1990’s,
        which captured our attention for 3 days straight. Little did we know that over 15 years
        later and following 10 years experience in the sports industry this would lead to setting
        up a volleyball destination.

        \n\nFor several years now we have been convinced that the sport of volleyball has been
        under-served by the mainstream media market and that whilst the current industry
        publications offer some great coverage of the sport there exists an opportunity to deliver
        fans the best quality content from around the world.

        \n\nOur team is made of sports industry professionals that have years of experience of working
        with and managing many of the world’s leading sports destinations including nba.com,
        premierleague.com, goal.com, sportal.com.au, foxsoccer.com, beinsports.com and
        footballaustralia.com.

        \n\nWe can’t claim that we’ll deliver everything that we want to from day 1 but we are
        committed to growing Volleyverse into a valued destination and resource for all volleyball
        fans globally. We need your input in order to achieve this so please don’t hesitate to get
        in touch via our Feedback page or our social media profiles. We can’t guarantee an
        immediate response but will always try to respond back to you wherever possible.
    </string>

    <string name="partnerships_body">
        Volleyverse’s objective is to deliver the best content to volleyball fans and provide a
        platform for our partners to engage with these users. We believe that we can deliver
        compelling, opinionated content delivered with integrity and maintain a professional
        product that our partners are proud to be associated with.

        \n\nWe don’t have any predefined ideas as to how we could work with partners, instead
        preferring to understand your objectives and work with premium brands to deliver value to
        all parties. We do prefer to work with partners to create engaging functionality or content
        over a period time as opposed to short term media deals.

        \n\nYou can download more information about Volleyverse below and welcome any genuine
        enquiries to dan.grey@volleyverse.com.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_and_cookie_policy_body">
        Five Rings Media Ltd

        \n\nLast updated: OCTOBER 3RD, 2015

        \n\nThis privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how Five Rings Media Ltd and its related
        companies collect, use and share personal data of users of this website,
        volleyverse.com.

        \n\nPlease take a moment to read this Policy which explains how we collect, use, disclose
        and transfer the personal information that you provide to us on our websites or mobile
        applications, when you visit our site.

        \n\nBy visiting our site and providing us with your personal data, you acknowledge and
        agree that your personal data may be processed for the purposes identified in this Policy.

        \n\nYou can find out more about Five Rings Media Ltd and the Terms of Use for using our
        site at Terms of Use.

        \n\nWHO WE ARE &amp; CONTACT INFORMATION

        \n\nFive Rings Media Ltd is a company with registered offices at 15 Balham New Road,
        London, SW12 9PH.

        \n\nWe welcome your comments about this Policy. If you have any questions about how we use
        your personal data, please do not hesitate to contact us at:
        \n15 Balham New Road
        \nLondon
        \nSW12 9PH
        \nE-mail: dan.grey@volleyverse.com
        \nPhone: +44 (749) 439-0882

        \n\nWHAT WE COLLECT

        \n\nWe obtain information about you in a range of ways:

        \n\nInformation You Give Us.

        \n\nWe collect your name, email address, username, password and demographic information
        (such as your gender and occupation) as well as other information you directly give us on
        our site. In addition, we may also collect personal information from you when you
        correspond with use (for example, when you send us e-mail communications or letters, or by
        telephone).

        \n\nInformation We Get From Others.

        \n\nWe may get information about you from other sources. We may add this to information we
        get from this site.

        \n\nInformation Automatically Collected.

        \n\nWe automatically log information about you and your computer. For example, when
        visiting our site, we log your computer operating system type, browser type, browser
        language, the website you visited before browsing to our site, pages you viewed, how long
        you spent on a page, access times and information about your use of and actions on our
        site.

        \n\nCOOKIES

        \n\nOur site (like most platforms) uses cookies and other similar technology such as ‘web
        beacons’.

        \n\nWhat is a Cookie?

        \n\nCookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to
        your computer or mobile device when you visit a website or mobile application. Cookies are
        then sent back to the originating site on each subsequent visit, or to another site that
        recognises that cookies. You can find out more information about cookies at
        www.allaboutcookies.org

        \n\nCookies are widely used in order to make sites work, or to work more efficiently, as
        well as to provide information to the owners of the platform.

        \n\nWe use cookies to enhance the online experience of our visitors (for example, by
        remembering your language and/or product preferences) and to better understand how our site
        is used. Cookies may tell us, for example, whether you have visited our site before or
        whether you are a new visitor. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are
        more relevant to you and your interests.

        \n\nTypes of Cookies

        \n\nThere are two broad categories of cookies:

        \n\nFirst Party Cookies, served directly by [name of business] to your computer or mobile
        device. They are used only by [name of business] to recognise your computer or mobile
        device when it revisits our site.

        \n\nThird party cookies, which are served by a service provider on our site, and can be used
        by the service provider to recognise your computer or mobile device when it visits other
        sites. Third party cookies are most commonly used for platform analytics or advertising
        purposes.

        \n\nCookies can remain on your computer or mobile device for different periods of time. Some
        cookies are ‘session cookies’, meaning that they exist only while your browser is open.
        These are deleted automatically once you close your browser. Other cookies are ‘permanent
        cookies,’ meaning that they survive after your browser is closed. They can be used by the
        site to recognise our computer or mobile device when you open your browser and browse the
        Internet again.

        \n\nWhat cookies do we use?

        \n\nOur Site uses the following types of cookies:

        \n\nType of cookie Purpose
        \nCookies necessary for essential purposes These cookies are essential to provide you with
        services available through our site and to use some of its features, such as access to
        secure areas. Without these cookies, services you have asked for, like transactional
        pages and secure login accounts, would not be possible.
        \nAnalytics Cookies These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our
        site.
        \nThe information gathered does not identify any individual visitor and is aggregated. It
        includes the number of visitors to our site, the sites that referred them to our site and
        the pages that they visited on our site.
        \nWe use this information to help operate our site more efficiently, to gather broad
        demographic information and to monitor the level of activity on our site.
        \nPerformance Cookies These cookies collect information about how visitors use the site, so
        that we can analyse traffic and understand how our visitors use our sites. We use Google
        Analytics for this purpose. Google Analytics uses its own cookies. These cookies don’t
        collect information that identify a visitor. All information these cookies collect is
        aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how the site works. You can
        find out more information about Google Analytics cookies here:
        https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies
        \nYou can avoid the use of Google Analytics relating to your use of our site by downloading
        and installing the browser plugin available via this link:
        http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB
        \nFunctionality Cookies These cookies allow our site to remember choices you make (such as
        your user name, or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features.
        These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and
        other parts of web pages that you can customize. They may also be used to provide services
        you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these
        cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other
        websites.
        \nSocial Media Cookies These cookies are used when you share information using a social media
        sharing button or “like” button on our sites or you link your account or engage with our
        content on or through a social networking site such as Facebook, Twitter or Google+. The
        social network will record that you have done this. This information may be linked to
        targeting/advertising activities.

        \n\nFurther detailed information about the specific cookies used on this site and the third
        parties who serve them can be found in our cookie consent tool [hyperlink to cookie consent
        tool]. You can use this cookie tool to control your cookie preferences.

        \n\nHow to control or delete cookies

        \n\nYou have the right to choose whether or not to accept cookies and we have explained how
        you can exercise this right below. However, please note that if you choose to refuse
        cookies you may not be able to use the full functionality of our site.

        \n\nYou can set your cookie preferences by using our cookie consent tool [hyperlink to
        cookie consent tool] or by changing your browser settings so that cookies from this site
        cannot be placed on your computer or mobile device. In order to do this, follow the
        instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “help” “tools” or “Edit”
        facility).

        \n\nFurther information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on
        your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them, visit
        www.allaboutcookies.org and www.youronlinechoices.eu.

        \n\nIP Addresses

        \n\nWe may collect information about your computer or mobile device, including where
        available your IP address, operating system, log in times and browser type. We use this
        information to better understand how visitors use our site and for internal reporting
        purposes. We may anonymise and share this information with advertisers, sponsors and/or
        other businesses.

        \n\nUSE OF PERSONAL DATA

        \n\nWe use your personal data for the following purposes:
        \n-to operate, maintain, and improve our sites, products and services;
        \n-to process and deliver the contest entries and rewards;
        \n-to respond to comments and questions and provide customer service;
        \n-to send information including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates,
        security alerts and support and administrative messages;
        \n-to communicate about promotions, upcoming events, and other news about products and
        services offered by us and our selected partners;
        \n-to link or combine user information with other personal data;
        \n-to protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal
        activity; and
        \n-to provide and deliver products and services at customers request.

        \n\nSHARING OF PERSONAL DATA

        \n\nWe do not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or
        non-affiliated companies outside Five Rings Media Ltd except under the following
        circumstances:
        \n- With your consent. For example, you may let us share personal data with others for
        their own marketing uses. Those uses will be subject to their privacy policies.
        \n- When we do a business deal, or negotiate a business deal, involving the sale or
        transfer of all or substantially all of our business or assets. These deals can include any
        merger, financing, acquisition, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.
        \n- For legal, protection, and safety purposes;
        \n\t- to comply with laws or any regulatory obligation;
        \n\t- to respond to lawful requests and legal processes;
        \n\t- to protect the rights and property of Five Rings Media Ltd, our agents, customers and
        others. This includes enforcing our agreements, policies and Terms of Use.
        \n\t- in an emergency. This includes protecting the safety of our employees and agents, our
        customers, or any person.
        \n- With those who need it to do work for us.

        \n\nWe may also share aggregated and/ or anonymised data with others for their own uses.

        \n\nINTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA

        \n\nYour personal data may be collected, processed and/or otherwise transferred outside the
        European Economic Area and may be processed not only in the country in which it was
        collected but also in other countries, including the United States, where data protection
        and privacy laws and regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other
        parts of the world. By providing your personal data to us, you consent to such transfer,
        collection and/or processing in the United States of your personal data, which includes the
        use of cookies as described in this Policy, which includes the use of cookies as described
        in this Policy.

        \n\nPROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION

        \n\nWe want you to feel confident about using our site, and we are committed to protecting
        the personal information we collect. We limit access to personal information about you to
        employees who reasonably need access to it, to provide products or services to you or in
        order to do their jobs. We have appropriate technical and organisational physical,
        electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the personal information that you provide
        to us against unauthorised or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, damage or
        destruction.

        \n\nHOW TO EDIT, DELETE OR ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL DATA

        \n\nYou have the right to ask for a copy of any personal information that we hold about you
        in our records, to correct any inaccuracies and to update any out of date information. You
        can also ask us not to send you direct marketing communications (however please note that
        we may continue to send you service related (i.e. non-marketing) communications, such as
        email updates). If you wish to exercise any of these rights, or wish to object to our use
        of your personal information, please write to us at the address given above.

        \n\nCHILDREN

        \n\nThis site is not directed at anyone who we know to be under the age of 13, nor do we
        collect any personal information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 13. If you
        are under the age of 13, you should not use the platform and should not submit any personal
        information to us.

        \n\nCHANGES TO THIS POLICY

        \n\nFrom time to time we may change this Policy. If we make any changes, we will change the
        Last Updated date above. If you do not agree to these changes, please do not continue to
        use our site. If material changes are made to this Policy, we will notify you by email or
        by placing a prominent notice on the site.
    </string>

    <!-- Lint thinks that (c) should be a copyright symbol. Suppressing the warning. -->
    <!--suppress AndroidLintTypographyOther -->
    <string name="terms_of_use_body">
        LAST REVISED ON: OCTOBER 3RD 2015

        \n\nThe website located at volleyverse.com (the “Site”) is a copyrighted work belonging to
        Five Rings Media Ltd (“Company”, “us”, “our”, and “we”). Certain features of the Site may
        be subject to additional guidelines, terms, or rules, which will be posted on the Site in
        connection with such features. Without limitation to the preceding sentence, your
        submission of information, including personal information, through or in connection with
        the Site is governed by the terms of our privacy policy as updated from time to time,
        available at Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”).

        \n\nAll such additional terms, guidelines, and rules, including our Privacy Policy, are
        incorporated by reference into these terms of use (these “Terms”).

        \n\nThese Terms set forth the legally binding terms and conditions that govern your use of
        the Site. By accessing or using the Site, you are accepting these Terms (on behalf of
        yourself or the entity that you represent), and you represent and warrant that you have
        the right, authority, and capacity to enter into these Terms (on behalf of yourself or the
        entity that you represent). If you do not agree with all of the provisions of these Terms,
        do not access and/or use the Site.

        \n\n1. ACCOUNTS
        \n1.1 Account Creation. In order to use certain features of the Site, you must register for
        an account (“Account”) and provide certain information about yourself as prompted by the
        account registration form. You represent and warrant that: (a) all required registration
        information you submit is truthful and accurate; (b) you will maintain the accuracy of such
        information. You may delete your Account at any time, for any reason, by following the
        instructions on the Site. Company may suspend or terminate your Account in accordance with
        Section 8.

        \n\n1.2 Account Responsibilities. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of
        your Account login information and are fully responsible for all activities that occur
        under your Account. You agree to immediately notify Company of any unauthorized use, or
        suspected unauthorized use of your Account or any other breach of security. Company cannot
        and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with the
        above requirements.

        \n\n2. ACCESS TO THE SITE
        \n2.1 Licence. Subject to these Terms, Company grants you a non-transferable, non-exclusive,
        revocable, limited licence to use and access the Site solely for your own personal,
        non-commercial use.

        \n\n2.2 Certain Restrictions. The rights granted to you in these Terms are subject to the
        following restrictions: (a) you shall not license, sell, rent, lease, transfer, assign,
        distribute, host, or otherwise commercially exploit the Site, whether in whole or in part,
        or any content displayed on the Site; (b) you shall not modify, make derivative works of,
        disassemble, reverse compile or reverse engineer any part of the Site; (c) you shall not
        access the Site in order to build a similar or competitive website, product, or service;
        and (d) except as expressly stated herein, no part of the Site may be copied, reproduced,
        distributed, republished, downloaded, displayed, posted or transmitted in any form or by
        any means. Unless otherwise indicated, any future release, update, or other addition to
        functionality or content of the Site shall be subject to these Terms. All copyright and
        other proprietary notices on the Site (or on any content displayed on the Site) must be
        retained on all copies thereof.

        \n\n2.3 Modification. Company reserves the right, at any time, to modify, suspend, or
        discontinue the Site (in whole or in part) with or without notice to you. You agree that
        Company will not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension,
        or discontinuation of the Site or any part thereof.

        \n\n2.4 No Support or Maintenance. You acknowledge and agree that Company will have no
        obligation to provide you with any support or maintenance in connection with the Site.

        \n\n2.5 Ownership. Excluding any User Content that you may provide (defined below), you
        acknowledge that all the intellectual property rights, including copyrights, patents,
        trade marks, and trade secrets, in the Site and its content are owned by Company or
        Company’s suppliers. Neither these Terms (nor your access to the Site) transfers to you or
        any third party any rights, title or interest in or to such intellectual property rights,
        except for the limited access rights expressly set forth in Section 2.1. Company and its
        suppliers reserve all rights not granted in these Terms. There are no implied licences
        granted under these Terms.

        \n\n3. USER CONTENT
        \n3.1 User Content. “User Content” means any and all information and content that a user
        submits to, or uses with, the Site (e.g., content in the user’s profile or postings). You
        are solely responsible for your User Content. You assume all risks associated with use of
        your User Content, including any reliance on its accuracy, completeness or usefulness by
        others, or any disclosure of your User Content that personally identifies you or any third
        party. You hereby represent and warrant that your User Content does not violate our
        Acceptable Use Policy (defined in Section 3.3). You may not represent or imply to others
        that your User Content is in any way provided, sponsored or endorsed by Company. Because
        you alone are responsible for your User Content, you may expose yourself to liability if,
        for example, your User Content violates the Acceptable Use Policy. Company is not obligated
        to backup any User Content, and your User Content may be deleted from the Site at any time
        without prior notice. You are solely responsible for creating and maintaining your own
        backup copies of your User Content if you desire.

        \n\n3.2 Licence. You hereby grant (and you represent and warrant that you have the right to
        grant) to Company an irrevocable, nonexclusive, royalty-free and fully paid, worldwide
        licence to reproduce, distribute, publicly display and perform, prepare derivative works
        of, incorporate into other works, and otherwise use and exploit your User Content, and to
        grant sublicences of the foregoing rights, solely for the purposes of including your User
        Content in the Site. You hereby irrevocably waive (and agree to cause to be waived) any
        claims and assertions of moral rights or attribution with respect to your User Content.

        \n\n3.3 Acceptable Use Policy. The following terms constitute our “Acceptable Use Policy”:

        \n\n(a) You agree not to use the Site to collect, upload, transmit, display, or distribute any
        User Content (i) that violates any third-party right, including any copyright, trademark,
        patent, trade secret, moral right, privacy right, right of publicity, or any other
        intellectual property or proprietary right; (ii) that is unlawful, harassing, abusive,
        tortious, threatening, harmful, invasive of another’s privacy, vulgar, defamatory, false,
        intentionally misleading, trade libelous, pornographic, obscene, patently offensive,
        promotes racism, bigotry, hatred, or physical harm of any kind against any group or
        individual or is otherwise objectionable; (iii) that is harmful to minors in any way; or
        (iv) that is in violation of any law, regulation, or obligations or restrictions imposed
        by any third party.
        \n(b) In addition, you agree not to: (i) upload, transmit, or distribute to or through the
        Site any computer viruses, worms, or any software intended to damage or alter a computer
        system or data; (ii) send through the Site unsolicited or unauthorized advertising,
        promotional materials, junk mail, spam, chain letters, pyramid schemes, or any other form
        of duplicative or unsolicited messages, whether commercial or otherwise; (iii) use the Site
        to harvest, collect, gather or assemble information or data regarding other users,
        including e-mail addresses, without their consent; (iv) interfere with, disrupt, or create
        an undue burden on servers or networks connected to the Site, or violate the regulations,
        policies or procedures of such networks; (v) attempt to gain unauthorized access to the
        Site (or to other computer systems or networks connected to or used together with the
        Site), whether through password mining or any other means; (vi) harass or interfere with
        any other user’s use and enjoyment of the Site; or (vi) use software or automated agents or
        scripts to produce multiple accounts on the Site, or to generate automated searches,
        requests, or queries to (or to strip, scrape, or mine data from) the Site (provided,
        however, that we conditionally grant to the operators of public search engines revocable
        permission to use spiders to copy materials from the Site for the sole purpose of and
        solely to the extent necessary for creating publicly available searchable indices of the
        materials, but not caches or archives of such materials, subject to the parameters set
        forth in our robots.txt file).

        \n\n3.4 Enforcement. We reserve the right (but have no obligation) to review any User
        Content, and to investigate and/or take appropriate action against you in our sole
        discretion if you violate the Acceptable Use Policy or any other provision of these
        Terms or otherwise create liability for us or any other person. Such action may include
        removing or modifying your User Content, terminating your Account in accordance with
        Section 8, and/or reporting you to law enforcement authorities.

        \n\n3.5 Feedback. If you provide Company with any feedback or suggestions regarding the
        Site (“Feedback”), you hereby assign to Company all rights in such Feedback and agree that
        Company shall have the right to use and fully exploit such Feedback and related
        information in any manner it deems appropriate. Company will treat any Feedback you provide
        to Company as non-confidential and non-proprietary. You agree that you will not submit to
        Company any information or ideas that you consider to be confidential or proprietary.

        \n\n4. INDEMNIFICATION. You agree to indemnify Company (and its officers, employees, and
        agents), including costs and attorneys’ fees, from any claim or demand made by any third
        party due to or arising out of (a) your use of the Site, (b) your violation of these Terms,
        (c) your violation of applicable laws or regulations or (d) your User Content. Company
        reserves the right, at your expense, to assume the exclusive defence and control of any
        matter for which you are required to indemnify us, and you agree to cooperate with our
        defence of these claims. You agree not to settle any matter without the prior written
        consent of Company. Company will use reasonable efforts to notify you of any such claim,
        action or proceeding upon becoming aware of it.

        \n\n5. THIRD-PARTY LINKS &amp; ADS; OTHER USERS
        \n5.1 Third-Party Links &amp; Ads. The Site may contain links to third-party websites and
        services, and/or display advertisements for third parties (collectively, “Third-Party Links
        &amp; Ads”). Such Third-Party Links &amp; Ads are not under the control of Company, and
        Company is not responsible for any Third-Party Links &amp; Ads. Company provides access to
        these Third-Party Links &amp; Ads only as a convenience to you, and does not review,
        approve, monitor, endorse, warrant, or make any representations with respect to Third-Party
        Links &amp; Ads. You use all Third-Party Links &amp; Ads at your own risk, and should apply
        a suitable level of caution and discretion in doing so. When you click on any of the
        Third-Party Links &amp; Ads, the applicable third party’s terms and policies apply,
        including the third party’s privacy and data gathering practices. You should make whatever
        investigation you feel necessary or appropriate before proceeding with any transaction in
        connection with such Third-Party Links &amp; Ads.

        \n\n5.2 Other Users. Each Site user is solely responsible for any and all of its own User
        Content. Because we do not control User Content, you acknowledge and agree that we are not
        responsible for any User Content, whether provided by you or by others. We make no
        guarantees regarding the accuracy, currency, suitability, or quality of any User Content.
        Your interactions with other Site users are solely between you and such users. You agree
        that Company will not be responsible for any loss or damage incurred as the result of any
        such interactions. If there is a dispute between you and any Site user, we are under no
        obligation to become involved.

        \n\n5.3 Release. Subject to applicable law, you hereby release and forever discharge the
        Company (and our officers, employees, agents, successors, and assigns) from, and hereby
        waive and relinquish, each and every past, present and future dispute, claim, controversy,
        demand, right, obligation, liability, action and cause of action of every kind and nature,
        that has arisen or arises directly or indirectly out of, or that relates directly or
        indirectly to, the Site (including any interactions with, or act or omission of, other
        Site users or any Third-Party Links &amp; Ads).

        \n\n6. DISCLAIMERS
        \nThe Site is provided on an “as-is” and “as available” basis, and, to the extent permitted
        by applicable law, Company (and our suppliers) expressly disclaim any and all warranties
        and conditions of any kind, whether express, implied, or statutory, including all
        warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title, quiet
        enjoyment, accuracy, or non-infringement. We (and our suppliers) make no warranty that the
        Site will meet your requirements, will be available on an uninterrupted, timely, secure, or
        error-free basis, or will be accurate, reliable, free of viruses or other harmful code,
        complete, legal, or safe.

        \n\n7. LIMITATION ON LIABILITY
        \nTo the maximum extent permitted by law, and subject to the final paragraph in this
        Section 7, in no event shall Company (or our suppliers) be liable to you or any third party
        for any lost profits, lost data, costs of procurement of substitute products, or any
        indirect, consequential, exemplary, incidental, special or punitive damages arising from or
        relating to these Terms or your use of, or inability to use, the Site, even if Company has
        been advised of the possibility of such damages. Access to, and use of, the Site is at your
        own discretion and risk, and you will be solely responsible for any damage to your device
        or computer system, or loss of data resulting therefrom.

        \n\nTo the maximum extent permitted by law, and subject to the final paragraph in this
        Section 7, our liability to you for any damages arising from or related to these Terms
        (for any cause whatsoever and regardless of the form of the action), will at all times be
        limited to a maximum of fifty pounds sterling (GBP 50). The existence of more than one
        claim will not enlarge this limit. You agree that our suppliers will have no liability of
        any kind arising from or relating to these Terms.

        \n\nThe exclusions in this Section 7 shall apply to the maximum extent permitted by law, but
        Company does not exclude liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence,
        fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation, or any other liability which may not be excluded by
        law.

        \n\n8. TERM AND TERMINATION. Subject to this Section, these Terms will remain in full force
        and effect while you use the Site. We may suspend or terminate your rights to use the Site
        (including your Account) at any time for any reason at our sole discretion, including for
        any use of the Site in violation of these Terms. Upon termination of your rights under
        these Terms, your Account and right to access and use the Site will terminate immediately.
        You understand that any termination of your Account may involve deletion of your User
        Content associated with your Account from our live databases. Company will not have any
        liability whatsoever to you for any termination of your rights under these Terms, including
        for termination of your Account or deletion of your User Content. Even after your rights
        under these Terms are terminated, the following provisions of these Terms will remain in
        effect: Sections 2.2 to 2.5, and Sections 3 to 9.

        \n\n9. GENERAL
        \n9.1 Changes. These Terms are subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial
        changes, we may notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided
        to us (if any), and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Site. You are
        responsible for providing us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the
        last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not
        capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail
        containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes
        described in the notice. Any changes to these Terms will be effective upon the earlier of
        thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you (if applicable)
        or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our Site.
        These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Site. Continued use of our
        Site following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes
        and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

        \n\n9.2 Electronic Communications. The communications between you and Company use electronic
        means, whether you use the Site or send us emails, or whether Company posts notices on the
        Site or communicates with you via email. For contractual purposes, you (a) consent to
        receive communications from Company in an electronic form; and (b) agree that all terms
        and conditions, agreements, notices, disclosures, and other communications that Company
        provides to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications
        would satisfy if it were be in a hardcopy writing.

        \n\n9.3 Entire Terms. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between you and us
        regarding the use of the Site.

        \n\n9.4 Waiver. A waiver by Company of any right or remedy under these Terms shall only be
        effective if it is in writing, executed by a duly authorized representative of Company and
        shall apply only to the circumstances for which it is given. Our failure to exercise or
        enforce any right or remedy under these Terms shall not operate as a waiver of such right
        or remedy, nor shall it prevent any future exercise or enforcement of such right or remedy.
        No single or partial exercise of any right or remedy shall preclude or restrict the further
        exercise of any such right or remedy or other rights or remedies.

        \n\n9.5 Headings and Interpretation. The section titles in these Terms are for convenience
        only and have no legal or contractual effect. The word “including” means “including without
        limitation”.

        \n\n9.6 Severability. If any provision of these Terms is, for any reason, held to be invalid
        or unenforceable, the other provisions of these Terms will be unimpaired and the invalid or
        unenforceable provision will be deemed modified so that it is valid and enforceable to the
        maximum extent permitted by law.

        \n\n9.7 Relationship between you and us. You confirm that you are acting on your own behalf
        and not for the benefit of any other person. Your relationship to Company is that of an
        independent contractor, and neither party is an agent or partner of the other.

        \n\n9.8 Assignment. These Terms, and your rights and obligations herein, may not be
        assigned, subcontracted, delegated, or otherwise transferred by you without Company’s prior
        written consent, and any attempted assignment, subcontract, delegation, or transfer in
        violation of the foregoing will be null and void. Company may freely assign these Terms.
        The terms and conditions set forth in these Terms shall be binding upon assignees.

        \n\n9.9 Governing Law and Jurisdiction. These Terms and any dispute or claim arising out of
        or in connection with their subject matter or formation (including non-contractual disputes
        or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the law of England and
        Wales. You agree that the courts of England and Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction to
        settle any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with the subject matter or
        formation (including non-contractual disputes or claims) of these Terms.

        \n\n9.10 Copyright/Trademark Information. Copyright &#169; 2015 Five Rings Media Ltd.. All rights
        reserved. All trademarks, logos and service marks (“Marks”) displayed on the Site are our
        property or the property of other third parties. You are not permitted to use these Marks
        without our prior written consent or the consent of such third party, which may own the
        Marks.

        \n\n9.11 Contact Information. If you wish to contact us in writing, or if these Terms
        require you to give notice to us in writing, please contact us at:
        \nDaniel Grey
        \nAddress:
        \n15 Balham New Road
        \nLondon
        \nSW12 9PH
        \nTelephone: +44 (749) 439-0882
        \nEmail: dan.grey@volleyverse.com
    </string>
</resources>
